

DMITRII LIKHACHEV

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

- **L** + 971-58-856-9932
- ☑ lihachevd87@gmail.com
- Dubai,UAE
- **in** My Linkedin
- My GitHub
- My Portfolio

EDUCATION

2021-2022

It-Incubator: React Frontend Developer RS School: JavaScript/Front-end #1 RS School: JavaScript/Front-end #0

2005-2010

Urals State University of Railway Transport, faculty of railway construction, speciality - Engineer

2007-2010

Urals State University of Railway Transport, faculty of Economics and Finance, speciality - Commerce specialist

LANGUAGES

- English, B1 (in progress)
- Russian, native

ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm frontend developer with experience about 1 year in creating SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript. Knowledge in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. I improving my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with newtechnologies, such as React Native. I usually spend my free time reading IT-literature, doing sports and improving my English. Open to your suggestions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

06.2022 - PRESENT

My projects as frontend developer (part-time):

Task-manager

• Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux (Toolkit), RestApi, Storybook Redux-thunk, Router-dom, Axios, Mui, Formik, Redux-Form, Jest

Social-Network

• Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux, RestApi, Router-dom, Axios, Ant design, Formik, Redux-Form, Jest

Mama-Pizza

• Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, RestApi, Router-dom, Axios

03.2022 - 06.22

Second educational projects:

Songbirds | Online-Zoo | Gem Pazzle |

• Stack: JS / CSS / SASS/ HTML

01.2022 - 03.22

First educational projects:

Travel | Momentum

Stack: JS / CSS / SASS/ HTML

2010 - 2022

Head engineer Railway Transport

Lead a construction team service of railway supervise the work of construction equipment preparation of reports on work planning and control of completed work financial responsibility, financial reporting development of technical documentation.

SKILLS

- React/Redux (Toolkit)
- TypeScript/JavaScript
- Axios/Rest API
- Unit Test/Jest
- StorvBook
- React router dom, React Hooks
 Git
- MUI/Ant Design
- Formik/React Hook Form
- Styled Components
- Postman
- HTML/CSS/SCSS